= www.kisskh.asia =
SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
After that day,
it feels like Luan Nian
has put a spell on me.
He unlocked the secret of my desire.
Did you notice?
You cannot control the feelings of love.
And all those years,
he made me long for more.
He drove me crazy and lived in my mind.
Shang Zhitao, are you sober?
Do you understand
what's going to happen next?
I spent six years
in this shameful, hidden relationship.
There were grievances, pain,
and joy.
Yet I can never
take the first step to leave him.
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
"YOU ARE NOT SUITABLE"
The interview is about to begin, Luke.
Shang Zhitao.
Hi. I am Liang Xin, Lime's HR manager.
You can call me Tracy.
Today, your chief interviewer
is Luke Luan.
If you're ready, let's begin.
Okay.
I am Shang Zhitao.
My English name is Flora.
I am from Harbin,
and I attended university in Nanjing.
I'm a fresh graduate.
I would love to work at Lime.
Tell me about your work experience.
MUTE, HANG UP, CAMERA
Have you done any internships?
If you have, tell us about that.
I have.
While I was in college,
I did some scenic area planning projects
with my classmates.
We planned the event's itinerary,
set up the stage, and worked on posters
and promotional texts.
How big was the project?
There wasn't much funding,
but we were very interested in it,
so we joined with the goal
of gaining experience in mind--
Okay.
Next.
Thank you, Shang Zhitao.
That's all for your interview.
Please go back and wait for our notice.
It wasn't a huge project,
but I gained a lot of experience.
Maybe I can share it with you?
No need. I need someone
with top-tier hands-on experience.
You're not suitable. Next.
Thank you.
Luke.
Is it possible for you to mind
your tone during interviews?
Let them finish speaking, at least.
Sure.
Yao Bei.
I failed the interview.
What happened?
Tao. I have to work overtime today.
Let's meet up and talk another day, okay?
It's okay. I just arrived downstairs
at the flat I'm renting.
Once I find my unit, I'll settle in.
Okay. Take your time planning.
Don't give up.
It's normal to be rejected
by a renowned company like Lime.
Getting in is like winning the lottery.
I know.
All right then.
TIANTONG DONGYUAN, SECTION 1
Looking for someone?
Sorry to bother you.
I'm the new tenant.
I contacted Zhang Lei.
He's the landlord.
Come in.
Your room is here.
It wasn't a huge project,
but I gained a lot of experience.
- Maybe I can share them with you?
- No need.
You're not suitable. Next.
He didn't even let me finish.
It's okay.
Man proposes, God disposes.
Tao. Have you arrived in Beijing?
Have you settled in?
How are your unit and your housemate?
I've arrived. Everything is good.
Don't worry.
FOLLOW-UP E-MAIL TO LIME ADVERTISING
REGARDING MY WORK EXPERIENCE
I AM AN ADVERTISING STUDENT AT JINLING
UNIVERSITY OF FINANCE AND ECONOMICS
I'VE FOLLOWED LIME'S OUTSTANDING WORK
IN BRANDING AND CREATIVE PLANNING
A habitual thief, aren't you?
You keep stealing
my detergent and shampoo.
Don't you dare make things up.
I could say you stole my rings
and earrings.
Liar!
My bracelet was on the sink counter.
When I came back ten minutes later,
it was gone.
Only you went to the toilet.
So you must be the thief.
I did not steal it.
If you slander us again,
I'll tear your mouth off.
You lost something?
Maybe we should call the police.
Who are you? Why are you in my house?
Right. Call the police.
Now.
Call the police. Where's your phone?
What gives you the right
to say whatever you want?
Look at how crazy you are.
You always look miserable.
No wonder you're single.
Your man lies in bed all day.
He doesn't go to work.
"Honey, wash my socks."
"Honey, wash my underwear."
"Wash it for me."
Is it fun washing someone's
dirty underwear?
- I do what I want.
- Don't fight.
- Don't hit her.
- Move!
Let her go!
Come.
Lock the door.
- Open the door!
You hit me. I'll call the police.
- Hello, 110?
I want to make a report.
Come in.
The shortlist
for this graduate recruitment.
Please sign it.
GRADUATE RECRUITMENT SHORTLISTED
CANDIDATES, 5. SHANG ZHITAO
Shang Zhitao?
I thought I rejected her
during the interview.
Yes. You did.
But Luke,
HR is all about diverse employment.
I wasn't born to be an HRBP.
We all went through a learning process.
Our company has fielded
many competent individuals,
but they're all too high up
and out of touch with reality.
If this continues,
the team will have problems.
But we can't recruit someone with
neither qualifications nor experience.
Is she a relative of yours?
Are you doubting my professionalism?
You didn't even let her finish.
After the interview,
she proactively sent me
supplementary materials about her project.
Her feedback in the background check
was the best.
I have discussed this with headquarters.
This time, I'll recruit
some down-to-earth fresh graduates.
Consider this an experiment of mine.
Besides, your Lumi
keeps asking me for more manpower.
Can you please support my endeavor
and sign on the paper?
Fine. This is a favor.
Sure. I owe you one.
The new recruits will report next Monday.
Find some time and meet with them.
You were at the training seminar
last year, right?
I wasn't able to answer those questions.
"Is office romance allowed?"
Tracy, you're the one who decides
who gets to join our company.
Please use your power wisely.
Okay.
I shall return and add
"No asking about
your superior's personal life"
and "No dating
between superiors and subordinates"
to the new recruit's manual
in black and white. Happy?
Congratulations. You've become
more and more professional.
I shall go now.
FARMHOUSE PORK
So, you won't file
a police report anymore?
I've checked with Lei.
He said they had already mentioned
moving out last month.
Why else would they pack up so quickly
and leave while we were hiding?
She stole my things. So be it.
She can have them. I don't need them.
Thank you for today.
I am Sun Yu. What's your name?
I am Shang Zhitao.
Shang Zhitao.
Thank you.
I've never asked you this.
What do you do for work?
Love business.
I work in sales for a dating site.
Isn't that love business?
Where are you from?
Me? I'm from Harbin.
But I went to university in Nanjing.
Nanjing?
My ex is from Nanjing.
I… Sorry.
Don't be.
He should be the one apologizing to me.
He kept saying the feelings had faded.
But I know he thinks
I'm not good enough for him.
In Beijing,
everyone has a price.
They are waiting for the best offer.
You're too good for him.
He will surely regret it.
Impossible.
I won't let him hurt me again.
You're right.
Don't let anyone hurt you again.
Exactly.
Screw love.
I will be rich.
I won't let stupid romance weigh me down.
You have my support.
I agree with you.
When we're self-sufficient,
love will come after us.
Good one.
Meeting you is the beginning
of my good fortune. Thank you.
Actually, I'm the lucky one.
It's my first day in Beijing,
and someone is buying me a meal.
You're so kind and brave.
People will queue up to buy you a meal.
Dig in. You haven't touched anything.
OFFER LETTER
BEIJING LIME ADVERTISING
DEAR SHANG ZHITAO…
Tao, can I come in?
Thank you for today.
What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
What happened?
I… I found a job.
You… You found a job?
- Where?
- Lime.
Lime?
Seriously?
The Lime that made
the Olympic advertisements?
Is this for real, Shang Zhitao?
Beijing Lime.
You're amazing!
I was about to give this to you.
You told me you were looking for a job.
I got this lucky charm from Yonghe Temple.
It will boost your career.
Thank you, Sun Yu.
- I really need it.
- You are so amazing.
Luke.
I need to tell you something.
An emergency?
Qipai is very happy
with the annual plan we proposed.
- So we sign now.
- No.
Something bad happened.
They plan to use our design proposal
for their secondary line brand.
And they want a discount. 30% discount.
No.
Their Asia Pacific regional manager said
that the secondary line brand
would be their main push this year.
If our design proposal
can help them boost this year's sales,
next year, they'll let us
handle the marketing
of all their brands under them.
That's not good either.
So we'll just lose the deal then.
I'd rather lose them.
They approved our proposal,
which means our ideas are good.
They can choose to implement our proposals
on whichever product they want,
but we won't give them a discount.
Our ideas are not for hawking,
where people expect us
to give them a huge discount.
Okay. I'll confirm
the quotation with Finance.
You look dashing today.
Handle the file.
- Morning, Luke.
So, he is Luke.
Morning, Luke.
Morning.
Luke.
I'm the new recruit, Shang Zhitao.
Thank you for recruiting me.
No need to thank me.
I did not recruit you.
In my eyes, you're not good enough.
Then, I shall thank Lime
for this opportunity.
I'll work hard.
I hope you'll pass the probation,
instead of just using us
to polish your resume before leaving.
I am incredibly lucky and honored
to be able to work
in this world-class advertising company.
I will do my best to stay here.
New hire? You know her?
Why would I know a nobody
from the labor market?
Who got him so upset
this early in the morning?
We spoiled him, didn't we?
Tracy.
Welcome to Lime China.
I am Liang Xin, the HR manager.
In our company culture, we address
each other by our English names.
So, please call me Tracy.
Allow me to brief you and show you around.
Come with me.
What you're seeing now
is an introduction to our company.
This is the Creative Division.
Are you sure they want
to change it this way?
It's the same as our first draft.
START
This is the Business Division.
The busiest division in our company.
I'll notify the supplier
about the client's request immediately
so that they can find a new venue.
The Commerce Division.
We have a business negotiation
this afternoon.
Get the collaboration proposal ready.
Let's begin.
This is the pantry.
There's a lounge in the back.
This is the public space.
You can use it whenever you want.
Recap of the situation. Last month…
There are several restaurants
near the office.
When you show your Lime work badge,
you'll get a 20% discount.
You'll find the details
in the employee manual.
Your probation period
will last for three months,
and you'll rotate through divisions.
Once you've decided to work
in a particular division,
you may end the rotational shift.
Have I made myself clear?
Yes.
Your first position
is in Business Division One.
You will work under…
Lumi.
Tracy.
Allow me to introduce.
Lumi, your mentor.
You'll be working for her.
- Hi, madam.
- Wow.
Are fresh graduates this nerdy nowadays?
Perhaps you can show her
the true colors of corporate life.
Please be nice to kids.
Don't be like Luke.
Tracy.
Come on. I have no filter.
But work is work.
Don't treat it like a joking matter.
Worry not, madam.
I'll work hard.
All right.
She'll work for me now.
Come. Let me show you your desk.
Don't worry.
You'll sit here.
Ms. Lumi.
I am Shang Zhitao. Or Flora.
No need to add "miss".
Just call me Lumi.
My English and Chinese names
are both Lumi.
That row there
is the offices of all the bigwigs.
And that one in particular, avoid it.
Mr. Luan's office?
You're smart.
At work, just call him Luke.
All right. I'll send you
some documents later.
Familiarize yourself with our projects,
and wait for my call.
Oh. Report yourself to Luke first.
While you do that,
conduct the interview as well.
Compile your questions now.
Interview?
I will interview Luke?
It is our tradition that the new hire
will interview the boss.
Book an appointment with him today.
Lumi.
- You startled me.
- Sorry.
I have a question.
Must I do the interview today?
You're afraid of him?
I heard he's quite strict.
I'm just a bit worried.
Creative people can be cranky.
He's blunt, but he can be reasoned with.
He won't devour you. Careful.
He has already vented his anger today.
He yelled at three people
until they cried at the morning meeting,
so he probably won't yell again.
What can I do to get along with him
if I don't want to be yelled at?
Get along with him?
Do you want to date him or something?
You're blushing.
I have one tip for you.
At work, the more prideful your boss is,
the more thick-skinned you have to be.
Thick-skinned?
Good luck.
Come in.
Hi, Luke.
I am Shang Zhitao,
the new hire in Business Division One.
You can call me Flora.
Do you have time now?
I have some questions for you.
Is it urgent?
Not really.
Not urgent?
Then, wait here.
She doesn't hide a thing.
You won't find
someone so guileless in Lime.
Hello.
Luan Nian.
I don't want to break up.
Can we…
Can we sit down and talk things through?
- Do not call me with a new number again.
- Luan Nian!
‪Luan--
Luke.
Are you free now?
You said it wasn't urgent.
I assumed your time wasn't worth much,
so your work could be deprioritized.
I understand now.
I will be direct about my needs
with you from now on.
Thank you for the lesson.
I did not teach you anything.
You may leave.
Luke, according to the company's policy,
you need to work with me as a new hire
to have the interview.
If you are not free today,
I'll follow up tomorrow.
Just do it now.
Sure.
Why did you join Lime?
The pay is great.
- Do you like your job?
- No.
Then, why are you staying?
To make money and splurge.
Okay.
Allow me to share the projects I will be
joining in the future with you one by one.
- I look forward to your further guidance.
- I will not guide you.
You can just ask Lumi for anything.
But I hope you can--
Can you differentiate ROI and CVR?
Can you use SWOT analysis
to market a product?
Can you differentiate
between advertising channels?
Sorry. Can you repeat?
I'll take them down
and try to get back to you by tomorrow.
If you really want a piece
of advice from me,
it'll be to find a new job
as soon as possible.
You're not fit for Lime.
Why do you think
I'm not a good fit?
Academics-wise, you're average.
Background-wise, you have no connections.
Experience-wise, you have no experience
with large-scale advertising projects.
What do you bring to the table?
Why should I waste my time
on someone who will be replaced soon?
I have been accepted into Lime.
That means I must have some value.
I will do my best to keep up with you.
I won't waste your time.
You're wasting everyone's time.
You can't even understand what I'm saying.
I don't deal with idiots.
What kind of person do you like
to deal with then?
- I can--
- I deal with jerks
ike me. Can you do that?
Okay.
Duly noted.
Thank you.
I will go now.
Sorry. I… I'll buy a new one.
You can't afford it. Get out.
Get out now.
SHANG ZHITAO
You must be the new intern.
No, I'm not.
I'm a full-time employee.
Today is my first day.
I am Shang Zhitao, Flora.
Hi, I'm Jack.
Are you free?
Can you get me a cup of coffee?
Sure.
Thank you.
Does anyone else want coffee?
You love making coffee that much?
Why don't you make everyone
a cup of coffee?
Lumi. Conference Room One.
- Meeting in ten minutes.
- Noted.
Iced Americano.
Flora, from now on in this company,
ask me before you do anything.
I am your mentor.
I'll tell you what to do.
Do you hear me?
- Yes.
- Don't be too meek.
In this office,
people will bully the weak.
The more sheepish you are,
the more they take advantage of you.
They will then ask you to do
all the hard labor.
You won't be able to take it.
Have you conducted the interview?
Yes.
Lumi.
Well, is the typewriter in Luke's office
very expensive?
I ran into it just now,
and he said I could never afford it.
You are quite something.
He loves that thing.
I'm not sure how expensive it is.
Meeting first. We'll talk after.
LEISURE WORK AREA
MINUTES OF MANAGEMENT INTERVIEWS
SEND
Q&A OF THE INTERVIEW
QUESTIONING OF PERSONAL CAPABILITIES
AND FUTURE PROJECTS
THE LEADER REPEATEDLY USED NEGATIVE
AND AGGRESSIVE LANGUAGE
DURING THE INTERVIEW
Hello?
You told the new hire
that you worked to splurge?
TO MAKE MONEY AND SPLURGE
Why are you staying
if you don't like the job?
To make money and splurge.
What else?
And you told her to find a new job.
I ADVISE YOU TO GET A NEW JOB
You're not fit for Lime.
Is that a problem?
And you want her to be a jerk?
What kind of person
do you like to deal with then?
I deal with jerks.
Is that a problem?
The advertisement industry needs us
to be bold and yet unfazed by anything.
Are you aware that your next promotion
is around the corner?
Does that have anything to do
with the interview?
Not directly,
but you must respect
our diversity employment policy.
I respect that,
but it has nothing to do
with my opinion of her.
What's so bad about her?
It's her first day at work.
If you weren't my junior,
I would've reported you to the board
and asked them to fire you.
Go ahead.
She's indeed an idiot.
JINGHUANANJIE STATION
OPERATION HOURS: 05:30-22:00
23:08, JUNE 21, THURSDAY
LOWER CARBON, GREENER LIVING
If you really want
a piece of advice from me,
it'll be to find a new job
as soon as possible.
You're not fit for Lime.
I'm staying, regardless.
Hang on. Where are you heading?
I have to hand over the shift soon.
I can't give you a ride
if we're not going the same way.
Tiantongyuan. Is that okay?
It's too far. Sorry.
I don't have enough petrol.
Want a ride? Where to?
- I… I'm going to Tiantongyuan.
- One hundred and twenty yuan.
That's too expensive.
Expensive?
Do you know what time it is?
No one goes there anymore.
Hop in. Let's go.
Hop in.
No, thanks. I found a cab.
It's illegal to stop here.
He's driving a Mercedes-Benz
and yet he's stealing my business.
JING Z 59Q00
Fasten your seat belt.
Thanks, Luke.
You may drop me off in front.
I'll hail a cab back.
Drop you off so that you can get
into another scam cab?
There was a piece of chewing gum
on that scammer's license plate.
The O on it became a Q.
Stop looking at it. Where do you stay?
Luke.
I live quite far away.
My home is in Tiantongyuan.
I don't want to trouble you.
You don't want to trouble me?
You wrote in the interview
that I asked you to quit.
HR said I couldn't make things up
for the interview,
so I was being honest.
You can be quite crafty.
Just a bit, though.
TIANTONG DONGYUAN
- Is this the place?
- Yes, it's here.
- Get out.
- Thanks.
Luke.
I am not challenging your authority.
I have noted down
everything you said today.
You noted it down?
Are you using it against me immediately
and being a jerk
or to get back at me?
No. HR told me
to write everything down truthfully.
Being only truthful
won't make you last in this industry.
You're not fit for Lime.
That's my real advice.
Go home now.
You…
Why do you hate me so much?
Is it because I ruined your typewriter?
I can compensate you.
Can I pay you back
through monthly installments?
It has nothing to do with it.
And you don't need to compensate me.
I'm so sorry.
I won't quit.
Thank you for the lift.
She looks meek,
as if anyone can bully her.
But when she's mad, she will fight back.
Just a little, that's all.
Sun Yu. Sun Yu.
Sun Yu!
Help!
LOWER CARBON, GREENER LIVING
I am incredibly lucky and honored
to be able to work
in this world-class advertising company.
I will do my best to stay here.
Hop in.